Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
ALL MEN'S SOULS ARE IMMORTAL
BUT TH E SOULS OF TH E RIGHTEOUS
ARE IMMORTAL AND DIVINE.
SOCRATES
My oracle... what vision did you dream?
Titans. . . unleashed
By whom?
King Hyperion
He seeks the Epirus bow
to rule over mankind .
We must pray.
Hyperion is here.
He comes for me.
We must go now.
SYBELLINE MONASTERY
GREECE 1228 B.C.
KOLPOS PENINSULA
My oracle.
You were presented with vision.
What have you seen?
The slave by the water.
He is touched by the gods.
If he embraces Hyperion
all of Greece will be destroyed .
Summon the guards.
Go. my oracle!
We will take care of the guards.
Go!
MOUNT TARTARUS
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org